<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gus Beane</title>
    <link>http://www.gusbeane.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Gus Beane</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.gusbeane.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Theme Demo</title>
      <link>http://www.gusbeane.com/posts/theme-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gusbeane.com/posts/theme-demo/</guid>
      <description>Style Demo h1 Heading h2 Heading h3 Heading h4 Heading h5 Heading h6 Heading This is bold text
This is bold text
This is italic text
This is italic text
Deleted text
This is text with inline math $\sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} = 1$ and with math blocks:
$$ \sum_{n=1}^{\infty} 2^{-n} = 1 $$
   Heading Another heading     text text   text text   text text     Block quotes are written like so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>http://www.gusbeane.com/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gusbeane.com/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>http://www.gusbeane.com/posts/hugo-template-primer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gusbeane.com/posts/hugo-template-primer/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>http://www.gusbeane.com/posts/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gusbeane.com/posts/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Goto hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your os and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at installing hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title>
      <link>http://www.gusbeane.com/posts/migrate-from-jekyll/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gusbeane.com/posts/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid>
      <description>Move static content to static Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.gusbeane.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gusbeane.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a senior undergraduate at the University of Pennsylvania. I study physics with a focus on astrophysics and cosmology. For the fall 2018 semester, I am working full-time at the Center for Computational Astrophysics.
I am primarily interested in high-redshift cosmology, and in particular the Epoch of Reionization. I am also interested in Milky Way dynamics and galaxy formation, with an overall emphasis on extracting science from numerical simulations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Actions Are Weak Stellar Age Indicators in the Milky Way Disk</title>
      <link>http://www.gusbeane.com/suppl-info/2018apj-867-31b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gusbeane.com/suppl-info/2018apj-867-31b/</guid>
      <description>Angus Beane, Melissa K. Ness, Megan Bedell
ApJ arXiv: 1807.05986 ADS: 2018ApJ&amp;hellip;867&amp;hellip;31B
Animated versions of Figures 5 and 6.    Figure 5. While young stars are clumped in action/velocity space, old stars are spread out - but not preferentially towards any part of action/velocity space.
   Figure 6. Each subplot rotates, to better visualize the 3D plot. While previosuly we only considered slices in action space, this 3D plots shows that there is no clear distinction in the entirety of action space between young and old stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://www.gusbeane.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gusbeane.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>abeane@sas.upenn.edu</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>http://www.gusbeane.com/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.gusbeane.com/research/</guid>
      <description>Measuring the EoR Power Spectrum Without Measuring the EoR Power Spectrum with Francisco Villaescusa-Navarro (CCA) and Adam Lidz (UPenn)
 Cleaning foregrounds from future EoR surveys may imprint artificial bias in the measured 21&amp;nbsp;cm power spectrum. Cross-spectra can be measured much more robustly in the presence of foregrounds. We show that if two line-intensity mapping surveys overlap with a 21&amp;nbsp;cm survey, then the 21&amp;nbsp;cm power spectra can be measured on large scales using only the cross-spectra between these fields.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>